thetraveltart.com 2016-11-21

# Privacy Policy - The Travel Tart Blog, Funny Photos, Videos, Advice

## Privacy Policy Updated and Effective: March 2, 2015

This following document sets forth the **Privacy Policy** for the TheTravelTart.com.

TheTravelTart.com is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our Web site. You can access TheTravelTart.com and browse our site without disclosing any of your personal data. TheTravelTart.com does not collect personal information about individuals, such as names and mailing or e-mail addresses, unless it is knowingly provided by the individual and he or she has agreed to the terms under which TheTravelTart.com will use it.

## Your Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

## Collection of Personal Information

When visiting TheTravelTart.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Use of your Personal Information

For each visitor to reach the site, we expressively collect the following non-personally identifiable information, including but not limited to browser type, version and [language](http://www.thetraveltart.com/tag/language/), operating system, pages viewed while browsing the Site, page access times and referring website address. This collected information is used solely internally for the purpose of gauging visitor traffic, trends and delivering personalized content to you while you are at this Site.

From time to time, we may use information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will use for these new purposes only, data collected from the time of the policy change forward will adhere to our updated practices.

## Disclosure of Information

TheTravelTart.com will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We collect only the personal data that you may volunteer while using our [services](http://www.thetraveltart.com/travel-writer/) (if any). We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.

TheTravelTart.com may release account information when such release is reasonably necessary to comply with the law; enforce the terms of any of our user agreements; or protect the rights, property, and safety of TheTravelTart.com, the users of its site, or others.

## Third Party Ads

Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, TheTravelTart.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

## External Web Sites

Please note that TheTravelTart.com contains [links](http://www.thetraveltart.com/travel-links-and-websites/) to other web sites. We have included links on this site for your use and reference. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or policies of these other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our site that you read the privacy statements of each web site that might collect personally identifying information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by TheTravelTart.com (if any).

On TheTravelTart.com, we hate spam, and we will never spam you or anyone else.

## Affiliate Disclaimer

TheTravelTart.com has financial relationships with some of the businesses mentioned in this website, and TheTravelTart.com may be compensated if consumers choose to apply for these links in our content and ultimately sign up for them.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

TheTravelTart.com reserves the right to make amendments to this Privacy Policy at any time. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Site.

## Contacting us

TheTravelTart.com welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy and would like further information, [please contact us](http://www.thetraveltart.com/international-travel/).

### About Anthony The Travel Tart

The [Travel](http://www.thetraveltart.com/tag/travel/) Tart writes about the funny, offbeat and [weird](http://www.thetraveltart.com/tag/weird/) aspects of world travel today. Travel wasn't meant to be taken too seriously! Check out ways to say hi below or [sign up for his silly newsletter!](http://thetraveltart.us6.list-manage1.com/subscribe/post?u=231ea8bfd220fe9854a414cdd&id=b87b46b560)
